## PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Tuan-Anh Bui

- Temasek Lab, SUTD, Room 3.719, 8 Somapah Road, Singapore
- **(+65)** 87415814
- <u>bta1489@gmail.com; tuananh\_bui@sutd.edu.sq</u>
- tuananhbui89.github.io
- Skype tuananhbui89
- in LinkedIn tuananhbui89

"If you want to live a happy life, tie it to a goal, not to people or things" - Albert Einstein

#### **OBJECTIVE**

With strong experience on an industry, I would like to bring a knowledge from academic to the real life through technological products, esp. using AI, Computer Vision to improve daily, common activities, to make the world to be a better place. I realize that pursuing Ph.D. is the must-do path to deepen my knowledge and improve the research methodology for this goal.

## RESEARCH BACKGROUND

Generative Adversarial Network, Detection and Tracking Moving Object, Image Retrieval Digital Signal Processing, Audio Processing (Viettel)

#### **EDUCATION**

## 09/2007-06/2012

## Hanoi University of Science and Technology, Hanoi, Vietnam (HUST)

BSc in Electronics and Telecommunications, Honour program, Talented class Thesis title: "Research on optimal trade-off between power saving and QoS"

Thesis grade: 4/4 (10/10) (Best Thesis Award)

GPA: 3.24/4 (8.44/10) (top 5% of SET Students, Merit for Excellent Graduate Student)

#### 08/2004-06/2007

## Le Hong Phong Gifted High School, Namdinh, Vietnam

High school Diploma, Physics Talented class

Got a Second prize in National Physics Olympiad for High School Students.

# WORKING EXPERIENCE

### 03/2017 - Present

#### **Research Assistant**

Temasek Lab, Singapore University of Technology and Design, Singapore Projects:

- Implemented module to detect and track Undefined Flying Objects, esp. Drone in Sky Surveillance Flying Object Detection (SSFOD) project.
- Improved image retrieval module to handle big dataset (approximate. 200k images) in Urban-area Scene Based Localization (USBL) project.

Research papers:

- Ngoc-Trung Tran, Tuan-Anh Bui, Ngai-Man Cheung, "Generative Adversarial Auto-Encoder Network", Under review ECCV18.
- Ngoc-Trung Tran, Dang-Khoa Le Tan, Anh-Dzung Doan, Thanh-Toan Do, Tuan-Anh Bui, Ngai-Man Cheung, "On-device Scalable Image-based Localization", under submission to Transaction on Image Processing, arXiv:1802.03510.

## 07/2012 - 03/2017

#### **Digital Signal Processing Engineer**

Viettel R&D Institute, Viettel Group, Hanoi, Vietnam

- Developed baseband processing algorithms: Channel equalization using adaptive filter, Adaptive Noise Cancellation, Digital Pre- Distortion to improve the linearity of radio amplifiers.
- Developed auto-control and measuring system for qualification and testing in manufacture.
- Won the internal contest, one of three best projects at Viettel for Developing and Manufacturing Viettel SDR Handheld Radio project, 2016.
- Got a Creative Idea Award at Viettel for Research and Management, 2012-2015.

#### 05/2010 - 06/2012

#### Research Assistant

Green Networking Lab, Hanoi University of Science and Technology, Vietnam

- Study on Openflow, Software Defined Networking, Traffic engineering, Energy consumption model, data centre network.
- Research on methods for reducing energy consumption in data centre network.
- Got a Third prize on Student Conference on Scientific Research.

## HONOURS & AWARDS

- 2016, Top 3, Best project at Viettel.
- 2012-2015, Creative Idea Award for Research and Management at Viettel R&D Institute.
- 2012, Merit for excellent graduate student, HUST.
- 2012, Best Thesis Award in Thesis Defence, SET, HUST.
- 2012, Third prize in Student Conference on Scientific Research.
- 2007, Second prize in National Physics Olympiad for High School Students.

#### **REFERENCES**

#### Assistant Professor Ngai-Man Cheung, Ph.D. (Supervisor)

Department of Information Systems Technology and Design Singapore University of Technology and Design E-mail: ngaiman\_cheung@sutd.edu.sg

#### Doctor Thu-Huong Truong, Ph.D. (Supervisor)

School of Electronics and Telecommunications Hanoi University of Science and Technology E-mail: huong.truong@hust.edu.vn

#### Mr. Hoang Nguyen (Manager)

Institute of Communication and Electronic Warfare Viettel R&D Institute, Viettel Group E-mail: hoangnc1@viettel.com.vn